GUSTAV GYRST

Puggaardsgade 18, 4tv, København V 1573 · 31769030 ggyrst@gmail.com · <u>LinkedIn</u> · <u>GitHub</u>

I am an MSc Software Design student studying at ITU with a business background (BSc in International Business) and work experience in a French scale-up. I love to code and drive change through analytics. *Learning* is what drives me. I am currently developing my analytical and technical skillset at ITU. Also, I love Jazz. I studied at the conservatory in Paris for two years after finishing high school.

EDUCATION

2020-NOW

MSC IN SOFTWARE DESIGN, THE IT UNIVERSITY OF COPENHAGEN

At ITU I have dived into the world of Computer Science head-first taking courses in Data Mining, Big Data Management (technical), AI, and more. I have worked with large datasets and developed ML models using regression, classification, and clustering models. I am currently pursuing my specialization in Business Analytics and writing my master thesis fine-tuning NLP algorithms to gain insights into how politicians talk about climate change in Denmark.

2016-2019

BSC IN INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS, COPENHAGEN BUSINESS SCHOOL

BSc in International Business is one of the hardest programs to enter in Denmark with a GPA requirement of 12.2. I completed the program with a GPA of 9.0. During my studies, I was a visiting student at both Bocconi (Milan) and the London School of Economics (London). Here I enjoyed statistics (grade 12) and game theory (grade A at LSE).

EXPERIENCE

2022 - NOW (ONGOING - PART-TIME)

TEACHING ASSISTANT IN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE, IT-UNIVERSITY OF COPENHAGEN

Currently, I am a TA for ITU's AI class lead by Professor Rune Møller. The class primarily revolves around symbolic AI algorithms such as A* (graph search), minimax, binary decision diagrams, and backtracking. The algorithms are applied to games such as othello, chess, and sudoku.

2019 - 2020 (12 MONTHS - FULL TIME)

INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT, ECOTREE

EcoTree is a French-based scale-up democratizing forests in Europe, so that individuals and companies can invest in sustainable forestry and help fight climate change. I was part of the founding team to open the Copenhagen office. We successfully raised 2 million euros in a venture capital series A in September 2019.

- I Signed our First Danish B2B clients
- Shaped our communication strategy and developed our B2C digital marketing content
- Optimized and built the international web-shops

2016 - 2017 (12 MONTHS PART-TIME)

RESEARCH AND ADMINISTRATION, COPENHAGEN BUSINESS SCHOOL

At the CBS research department of Strategic Management and Globalization, I worked as a student assistant assisting both with administrative matters and research. I took part in organizing the Strategy Summit of 2017.

SKILLS

- Languages: Danish, English, French, Python, Java, and SQL
- Python libraries and tools (Pandas, Scikit-learn, NLTK, Spark & more)
- Business Analytics and Statistics
- Communication and Public Speaking